Finding Aid for the Frederick Taylor Wolf Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Subject Files (Mostly Travel Files)
  - Southern Section - ASPP (Box 9)
  - Misc. -Personal, etc. (Box 9)
  - Program from the Fifth International Mycological Congress, Vancouver, Aug 14-21, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Plant Diagrams mounted on board (Box 9)
- Notebooks
  - Botany 41 Fall 1932 -Presses Specimen (Box 10)
  - Zoology 3- Harvard (Box 10)
  - Comparative Anatomy Lab - Harvard Fall, 1934 (Box 10)
  - Biology (Physiology) B - Dr. Stier, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Plant Physiology 146 Lecture Notes, 1936 (Box 10)
  - Plant Pathology 119 Forest Pathology, 1937 (Box 10)
  - Plant Pathology 117 Diseases of Orchard Fruits, 1938 (Box 10)
  - Chemistry 2 Organic Chemistry Dr. Fieser, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Chemistry 15 Biological Chemistry Dr. Henderson, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Botany 249 Physiology of Fungi, 1937 (Box 10)
  - Botany 220 Mycology (Box 10)
  - 302 Biology Dr. Greig (Box 10)
  - Plant Pathology 101 Reading (Box 10)
  - Plant Pathology 101 Lecture and Laboratory (Box 10)
  - Chemistry B (Sec. 5, Lab 306, Desk 189) (Box 10)
  - Chemistry 2 (Sec. A, Desk 163) (Box 10)
  - Genetics- Dr. Geckler (Box 10)
  - Chemistry 331 Physical Chemistry- Dr. Petersen (Box 10)
  - Botany 6 A, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Botany 6 A II, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Physics 1A Lecture and Quiz, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Physics 119-Radiation - Dr. Ingersoll, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Dr. Conant, 1948 (Box 11)
  - Mycology - Harvard, Spring 1934 (Box 11)
  - Anthopology A - Harvard, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Chemistry B (Box 11)
  - Chemistry 33 - Harvard, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Chemistry 2 - Dr. Fieser -, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Botany S-154 Notebook - UNC First Summer School, 1933 - Dr. Totten (Box 11)
  - Frederick Taylor Wolf - Thesis for PhD - Studies on the Aquatic Phycomycetes - Univ. of Wisconsin, 1938 (Box 11)
  - Frederick Adolf Wolf - Thesis for PhD - Life History and Development of Some Fungi - Cornell -, 1911 (Box 11)
  - 3 Bound Volumes of Published Articles by Frederick A. Wolf (Box 11)
  - Botany 2 Laboratory - Weston -Sinder Botany 2 II (Box 11)
  - Botany 41 Laboratory UNC Fall, 1932 (Box 11)
  - Chemistry 2 - Harvard, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Biology 16b Laboratory Drawings-, 1934-1935 (Box 11)
  - National Research Fellowships 1919-1938 from the National Research Council (Box 12)
  - Botany 108 Laboratory Morphology of Angiosperms (Box 12)
  - Ag Bacteriology 1 Lecture Notes - Dr. Sarles (Box 12)
  - Zoology 41-42 Laboratory UNC, Winter Spring 1933 (Box 12)
  - Botany 43 Lab UNC, Spring 1933 (Box 12)
  - High School Biology, 1928 (Box 12)
  - Studies on the Aquatic Phycomycetes- Thesis for PhD at Univ. of Wisconsin, 1938 (Box 12)
  - The Aquatic Phycomycetes of Wisconsin - Thesis for PhD at Univ. of Wisconsin, 1938 (Box 12)
  - Seminary in General Botany - Dr. C. E. Allen, 1935-1936 (Box 12)
  - Botany Lecture - Morphology of Bryophytes - Dr. Allen, 1938 (Box 12)
  - Botany 250 Cytology Lectures - Dr. Allen, 1937 (Box 12)
  - Botany 250 Cytology Lecture Notes - Dr. Allen, 1936 (Box 12)
  - Cytology Lectures Notes - Dr. L. C. Anderson Duke Univ., Summer 1938 (Box 12)
  - Zoology 42 Notes (Box 12)
  - Botany 41 Lecture Notes (Box 12)
  - Botany 43 Notes (Box 12)
  - Zoology 41 Lecture Notes - Mr. Reynolds, 1933 (Box 12)
  - Biology 115 - Economic Botany - Dr. Ames Plant Pathology 223 - Seminary, 1936 (Box 12)
  - Botany 108 Lecture Notes - Morphology of Angiosperms -, 1936 (Box 12)
  - Biology 115 - Economic Botany - Laboratory Notebook, 1934-1935 (Box 12)
  - Botany 2 I (Box 12)
  - Botany 214-215 - Seminary in General Botany and Plant Physiology, 1936-1937 (Box 12)
  - Botany 154 - Evolution of Plants - Dr. Allen (Box 12)
  - Botany 103 - Morphology of Algae - Dr. Allen -, 1936 (Box 12)
  - Mycology Biology 16b Research (Box 12)